A grassy plain, stretching as far as the eye can see.
I'm being watched. But from where?
That's been freedom.
You can fly again.
You can fly away.
The world is shining.
The sun is shining.
You are shining.
The moon is shining.
I think this is your beginning.
Closing in left.
I've got to wait here for Kilua.
Hey, sorry to make you wait.
Do you feel that?
Feels like somebody's watching us.
Yeah, and the gaze is definitely human.
So I'm not the only one.
Whoever it is can't be too good if we can sense them from here, so there's that.
Just ignore it.
We're being watched.
Kilua!
What's up?
I don't see any towns around here, do you?
I don't, but everyone is heading the same way.
Hmm. There or there?
Wait, how did you know that?
Because that's where whoever it is is watching from.
Unfortunately, we have no idea what they're watching us for.
Good point.
Well, whoever it is, we need to start gathering information.
Come on.
So, how did it go?
Hmm?
Your save data, of course.
Book.
How many cards were inside of it?
Uh, there weren't any.
What?
Really?
But there was a message from Jean.
What'd he say?
He told me to enjoy the game.
Enjoy the game?
Is that it?
The thing is, this just doesn't really feel like a game to me.
And book.
What do you think about all those rules that the girl explained to us?
Hmm.
Don't know enough yet.
I suppose we'll see.
What was that?
Was it Nen ability?
Let me guess.
This is your first time playing, huh?
Eh, who knows.
You must be a player.
You've got a book.
Ya think?
Hmm.
Can't fool me.
I know a newbie when I see one.
I can use the peek card.
What the hell is he doing?
Huh.
So you two are Killua and Gon, huh?
How do you know our names?
That is an excellent question.
If you don't know about spell cards, you don't stand a chance.
There.
That settles it.
There are a couple of noobs who just got here.
And they're only kids.
This one's too good to waste on them.
Trace should do it.
Trace on!
Attack Killua!
You can't run away from the spells in this game, kid!
Killua!
You okay?
Hehehehe.
So it worked.
What...
was that?
This kid is dangerous!
Return on!
Masadora!
Shizuku!
Kortopi!
Hmm?
You got a minute?
Play?
Yeah.
Do you want to go with me?
There's nothing to do at home once we get there anyway.
You really want to clear this game?
Actually...
Clearing it's not really my goal.
So...
Does this relate to troop business?
Maybe.
I got it.
Okay.
So...
How are you holding up, Kilo?
I'm holding up.
You got a minute?
Play?
Yeah.
Do you want to go with me?
There's nothing to do at home once we get there anyway.
You really want to clear this game?
Actually...
Clearing it's not really my goal.
So...
Does this relate to troop business?
Maybe.
I got it.
Okay.
So...
How are you holding up, Killua?
Oh.
I don't feel any different.
Good.
But I'm still worried.
That guy definitely did something to you.
There's no point stressing about it.
Hey.
Did you see if he was using Nen when he said trace on?
No.
It's probably magic that only works in the game.
Magic?
What kind?
Don't know.
But...
We'll find out soon enough.
Right.
Look!
There's a town!
Those must be the prizes.
Wow!
All of them?
It seems like it.
Hey!
Killua!
Look!
On Tokiba Monthly Tournament Schedule.
This month is Rock Paper Scissors!
And the prize is the Sword of Truth.
So...
Is that an important item?
Probably so.
Check it out.
There too.
You wanna play?
Of course.
Then since we're here anyway, let's enter lots of contests and stuff.
But we should also gather information.
Welcome!
Finish this within 30 minutes and it's free!
You'll also receive a Gargider as your prize!
Your time begins right now!
Oh man, so do you know how to use any magic?
What is that?
Oh!
And who's the wisest person in this city?
Wisest?
What is that?
This guy doesn't really know anything.
Really?
I bet he's just an NPC or something.
Wow!
You did it!
Here.
You boys have earned your Gargider.
1217.
And F185.
Hey, wait.
What does that mean?
Oh, is this your first time seeing a card?
The left number is the item's card number.
And the sequence on the right ranks how difficult it is to obtain.
There are ten ranks in all, from SS to H. F would be the third easiest, you see.
And the number right next to the rank is the item's maximum conversion limit.
Hmm.
And that means that this item card...
Yeah.
This is unplayable.
Never seen him before.
That's brutal.
He entered the game with us.
Hey, so what happened here?
His body suddenly exploded.
Just blew up from the inside.
We've only been playing for a few hours, and there's already a fatality.
The corpse is real.
He really is dead.
This doesn't seem like a game at all.
We really are risking our lives here.
He vanished?
He went back to the real world.
Game over.
Hey, Killua.
Do you think that the magic that guy used on you earlier?
I don't know.
Don't worry.
There are no spells in this game that are anything like that.
Spell, sir?
Like you said.
It's something akin to magic.
One thing's for certain.
He died from another player's nin.
Really?
Does that mean...
The players here are trying to kill each other?
Why would they do that?
It's player hunting.
Player hunting?
I can explain everything to you later.
Anyway, you two want to team up?
I know of a surefire way we can clear this game.
Uh-huh.
If you're interested, follow me.
Meet the rest.
They're waiting up ahead.
What now?
Well, sounds suspicious.
And we're already off to a pretty bad start.
Not to be rude.
But on your way here, didn't another player use an attack spell on you?
Have you been spying on both of us?
Tell me the truth.
Sure.
And not just me.
Lots of people are trying to kill each other.
I know of a surefire way we can clear this game.
Uh-huh.
If you're interested, follow me.
Meet the rest.
They're waiting up ahead.
What now?
Well...
Sounds suspicious.
And we're already off to a pretty bad start.
Not to be rude.
But on your way here, didn't another player use an attack spell on you?
Have you been spying on both of us?
Tell me the truth.
Sure.
And not just me.
Lots of people around here keep an eye on brand new players at the starting point.
If you come with me, I'll explain why.
And tell you all about the spell that was cast on you.
You're sure being pretty generous.
There's gotta be a catch in there somewhere.
We don't have a choice.
Once you realize how hard this game is,
not to mention how foul and frightening it could be,
I'm willing to bet you'll be a lot more happy to accept our offer.
And you're newbies, so you could definitely use the information.
On your first time playing here, take all the help you can get.
What makes you think it's our first time?
We could be returning players.
Even veterans for all you know.
Book.
That jump is all I need to prove that you're both beginners.
An experienced player would have reacted much differently to that,
by summoning his own binder.
Because you need spell cards to defend yourself.
That means the spell cast on Killua can't be stopped without a card.
Even when you're not carrying any cards,
you should still summon your binder.
It's an important bluff.
Book.
So, how do we obtain our own spell cards?
Well, the easiest way is to travel to Masadora, the city of magic.
Masadora?
Return on!
Masadora!
Hey, you wanna go?
I'm a little bit worried about the spell on you.
Come on!
Okay.
Is this everyone?
Yeah.
Everybody else turned me down flat.
Fine.
Then let's begin.
Just now, yet another player was found murdered.
He arrived here at the same time as the rest of you did.
His stomach exploded.
It was the bomber again.
Who?
His victims aren't killed by spells.
There isn't a spell in this game that's capable of injuring someone.
So don't worry.
No matter what happens,
you won't be harmed or killed by any spell that's been cast on you.
There are 40 different spells in all.
The one that was cast on you earlier was an inspection spell.
So it has to be either trace or cling.
In short, once the enemy uses one of these on you,
he will instantly know everything there is to know about you.
I get it.
So that's why...
Some people choose to wait for new players by the starting point.
That way, they can cast a spell on them quite easily.
As soon as a player obtains a valuable card,
they'll show up and steal it.
In some cases, they just kill their target.
Like the guy who just died?
Well, it won't be that easy to kill me.
No.
He was killed by someone else.
By a radical type of player who hunts his opposition.
The man who died was killed by someone called the Bomber.
Bomber.
In this game, there are only three ways that a player can acquire item cards they can use.
Know what they are?
Hmm.
Find them yourself.
You can also trade for them with other players.
Or simply steal them from other players.
Yes.
Those are the three possible ways.
However, the number of players stealing from others has increased.
That's because of the card's acquisition difficulty and conversion limit.
Players who can't obtain cards themselves often choose to take them from others.
If those players resist, they're killed by it.
Their ring disappears and the cards are lost.
But it increases the conversion limit for that type of card.
If you kill a player, you can't take his cards.
That rule was put in place to prevent players from killing each other.
But lately, it's been backfiring.
It's been over ten years since this game was first released.
If no one can find a way to beat it, the killing will only continue.
That's why all of us are all trying to end this mess.
We need more allies to clear the game.
That's where you come in.
How do you plan to obtain cards?
One, find them.
Two, trade for them.
Three, steal them.
Which are you gonna do?
Steal them.
I have to assume we'll be using all three.
But that'll be the primary method.
Hold on.
So you're still gonna use force?
No.
We refuse to use violence to achieve our goal.
Spells.
You just use spells, correct?
That's right.
There are spells that exist for taking others' cards.
As well as cards that defend against them.
We plan to monopolize those spell cards.
We're going to use the very same card conversion limit.
That's been frustrating us.
It's the only way to clear the game.
I've met a lot of players and they've all reached the same conclusion.
Every card you find will be taken from you eventually.
Because that's what the game is based on.
Taking cards from each other.
We take cards from others while mitigating our own risk of losing cards.
You're leaving out something important, aren't you?
How you gonna split the reward money once you clear the game?
Good point.
Mr. Batera hired all of you guys, didn't he?
You knew who we were when you found us?
Yeah.
You see, Mr. Batera hired all of us to play the game too.
That means the reward will be 50 billion.
We'll split it between everyone who helps us.
We have 53 players.
Two months to collect the remaining spell cards.
One to get the cards we need.
Three months to finish.
Of course, if you decide to join us,
we'll remove any spells that were cast on you.
I'm in.
Can't say I like the idea of splitting the 50 billion,
but I do like the idea of clearing the game in three months.
What about you?
I have a question.
So, if I get an SS rank card on my own, what's my cut?
Roughly.
SS?
For one of that rank?
It's about 500 million.
Okay.
I'm in.
What about you, kid?
You in?
Killua.
Sorry.
For what?
Count me out.
I'm playing on my own.
Well, you guys heard the boss.
I gotta pass.
Hey, Gon!
Wait up!
What about you?
First, we'll need you to exit the game,
so the spells placed on you can be removed.
Once you've re-entered the game, just wait for us by the starting point.
We'll come get you.
And if you have any cards in your free slots,
I'll need for you to give them to me now.
Why's that?
When you leave the game,
the cards left in your free slots disappear completely.
Yeah, but your data automatically saves when cards are put into or taken out of the specified slots.
That's true.
But your data disappears if you don't return within 10 days.
And if you don't return to the game before then, unfortunately,
we'll have to assume that you gave up.
Got it?
Don't worry.
A friend is joining us.
We don't know if anyone's watching.
Let's begin.
First off, I'll use the leave card.
Hey!
Wait up, Gon.
You wanna tell me what that was all about?
Sorry, Killua.
But I guess I just couldn't take it anymore.
Okay, but I still don't get why you're apologizing.
Because you're gonna be stuck with that spell for a while and it's all my fault.
Okay, I get it now.
Look, it's no big deal.
It is.
You're playing this game because of me.
You're only here to help me find my dad.
You're wrong.
I'm playing this game because...
So anyway, why'd you get so mad?
It's because they said mean stuff about Gene's game.
How it's all based on killing and stealing cards.
And I guess it really ticked me off.
I wanna do what Gene said to do and just enjoy the game.
When I first got here, I knew it wouldn't be easy, but I wasn't afraid.
Because I thought...
Well, I figured all the players genuinely enjoyed the game, you know?
People actually die here.
But the game, it's not scary.
It's that players hurt each other.
All over getting some cards.
That's the really scary part.
Really?
I think it makes sense.
Hey!
You really mean that?
It's dangerous, but it's just meant for hunters.
Still...
Killing is wrong, sure.
No argument on that part.
But what if two players each put forth a card, and the one who wins a battle with defined rules gets to keep both?
Uh, that's okay.
See?
When that guy casts a spell on me, and those guys start their strategy, they're only following the rules of the game.
But to be honest, it kind of feels like they're chickening out.
Look, forget about them, alright?
Let's just enjoy the game by ourselves.
Killua.
Thanks a lot.
I'm glad you're here with me.
No.
I'm really glad I met you in the first place.
Idiot!
This is embarrassing!
No it's not!
How can it be embarrassing if I mean it?
I'm sorry, Gon.
But you've got it backwards.
I'm the one who's glad I got to meet you.
I really am.
I see.
So that's why.
The friendship and innocence of two young boys is such a beautiful thing.
It would be so much fun to ruin it.
Gon and Killua have reaffirmed their friendship.
But what about the little girl watching them?
Who is she?
And what does she want?
What kind of world is waiting for you?
I'm waiting for you.
It's not like the sound of one.
I won't go away.
I'm waiting for you.
I don't forget.
消せない
今日の東海も
投げ捨て
朝日に
照らされた傷
笑い張って
終わることない
旅を
続けよう
向かい風と
していながら
それでも進む
理由がある
おいでくためだけに生きるのは
まだ
早いだろ
身につけたもの
破壊込んだもの
手放したとき
始まるなにか
うまく生きてく
レシピを
破り捨てて感じる
リズム
僕らのやり方で
関門では
無事が自分が溶かった
人々に
You